question_data = [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
        },
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a "
                     "building.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The "
                     "Reckoning&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in "
                     "&quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in &quot;Forza Horizon 3&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS "
                     "port of the game. ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
